voxbone.com 2018-08-30

# Voxbone | Privacy Policy

VOXBONE, S.A takes your privacy seriously. We store your data safely and handle it with the utmost care and in line with the provisions of the Belgian Data Protection Law of 8th December 1992 and the General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679.  

This Privacy Policy governs the use of the site www.voxbone.com and the services offered by the company VOXBONE, S.A (hereinafter, VOXBONE) with registered office at Avenue Louise 489, 1050 Brussels, Belgium, and holder of the VAT number VAT BE 0478.928.788. This site is available to users interested in the services offered on the site.  

By accepting the terms of this privacy policy, the user consents to the automatic processing of the personal data provided, with the purposes herein specified.

## Processing of personal data

When you register for VOXBONE services or when you request information, we may ask you to provide personal data. This data will include the following personal information:

Type of request | Data collected  
---|---  
  
  *  Contact forms (new customers and prospects)  
Abuse report cases  
Become a commercial partner  
Free trial account  
Register an account

| 

  * Full name, business email address and phone number

  *  Subscription to the newsletter

| 

  * Full name and email address (can be private)

  * Job application

| 

  * Full name, email address, phone number, address and the content of your CV

Once you become a Customer or a selected candidate for a published role, we may also ask you for other information that relates to the service you are using or ordering, or related to your job application. For example, for Customers, we may need your credit card number to charge you for certain services and proof of ID (end users), where there is a regulatory requirement to do so.  

You can view and edit your personal information at any time after registration with VOXBONE. You can stop the delivery of VOXBONE newsletters by following the instructions in the e-mail you receive. You may also request to correct, update or delete your personally identifiable information. In order to better protect you and safeguard your information, we take steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections to your information.

If you become a Customer, VOXBONE will store your personal data for the duration of the provision of the services to you. Specific data, such as traffic data, shall be kept as required by data retention laws of each country where such traffic data belongs to. Once the contract is terminated and/or the required retention period has expired, we will delete or anonymize the data. If you become a temporary selected candidate for a specific job, we will store your personal data for the duration of the selection process. If you become an unsuccessful candidate, we will request your consent if you want us to keep your data, should a future opportunity arises.

## Purposes of the processing

VOXBONE will only use your personal information for the following purposes:

  * manage your Customer account;
  * provide the services and/or information you have requested from us;
  * inform you of additional features, expanded coverage or other products or services offered by VOXBONE;
  * management of possible incidents;
  * check and measure the quality of the services offered;
  * comply with applicable regulatory, financial and accounting duties;
  * market research and statistics; and
  * unless otherwise indicated, to send commercial communications related to the requested service.
  * Manage your job application

## Third parties

We do not sell, rent, or lease our Customer lists to third parties and we will not share your data with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. However, our services may include the processing of personal data by third parties we work with in the following cases:

  * For the display of personalized advertising (Retargeting). You may find additional information in our [Cookie Policy](https://www.voxbone.com/cookie-policy).
  * To keep track of your interactions with our sites and services to offer a personalized experience. You may find additional information in our [Cookie Policy](https://www.voxbone.com/cookie-policy).
  * Suppliers we may need to work with in order to render the services adequately.
  * Our career site supplier iCIMS. If you are a job applicant, you may find more about [how iCIMS processes personal data here](https://www.icims.com/gc/data-security-privacy-policy).

We guarantee that any provider we work with that might be involved in the processing of your personal data, must be subject to the same privacy and IT security requirements as VOXBONE.

VOXBONE may also provide links to third-party websites as a service to our users. If you use these links, you will leave our site. Such links do not constitute or imply an endorsement, sponsorship, or recommendation by VOXBONE of the third party and it shall not be held responsible or liable for your use thereof. Such use shall be subject to the terms of use and privacy policies applicable to those sites.  

## User rights

You can view and edit your personal information at any time after registration with VOXBONE, through the web portal that will be made available to you to manage your account with us. Regarding commercial communications, you may also interrupt the delivery of VOXBONE newsletters by following the instructions in the emails you receive. 

You may, at any time, withdraw your consent for the processing of your personal data as well as exercise your rights of Access, Rectification, Erasure, Restriction, Objection and Data Portability (the latter, where applicable) by sending an email to privacy@voxbone.com or a letter to the following address: VOXBONE, S.A – Privacy, Avenue Louise 489, 1050 Brussels, Belgium. In either case, you must attach a copy of your valid National ID Document or Passport, providing your full name, contact details and the right you wish to exercise.

We inform you that the processing of the data you provide is essential for the provision of our services, for the management of job applications and for compliance with regulatory requirements applicable to the telecommunications sector. By choosing to delete some types of personal information, you may prevent us either from supplying certain services to you as a Customer or from continuing with your job application in the case of candidates.

## Veracity of the information provided by the user

You guarantee that the personal information provided is accurate and truthful and agree to notify VOXBONE of any changes in regards to such data.

You shall be responsible, in any case, for the veracity of the information provided. VOXBONE reserves the right to terminate the service provided to any user who has provided false or untruthful information from the services registered, without prejudice to other actions specified by applicable laws.

## Data transfers to third countries

For the processing of Customer data and in order to render a customized service to each Customer or Prospect, VOXBONE (i) may access European Customer data from its offices located in the USA and (ii) for account management purposes, it may require to use tools and software with servers located outside the European Economic Area and/or non-whitelisted countries. In the first case (i), the processing is carried out in line with the provisions of the European Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (‘GDPR’). In the second case (ii), the suppliers of these tools and software have either agreed to the EU Commission’s Standard Contractual Clauses or are Privacy Shield certified in order to guarantee the same privacy standards as those provided within the European Economic Area.

## Security measures

VOXBONE maintains a high level of protection of personal data and has established all the technical means at its disposal to prevent the loss, misuse, alteration, unauthorized access and theft of the data provided by the user. In order to better protect you and safeguard your information, we may ask you certain information in order to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections to your information.

Furthermore, we inform you that all personal data is protected in our systems and that only employees requiring the data for the purposes of rendering the services or complying with regulatory requirements will have access to information of this kind.

VOXBONE complies with the duty of secrecy and confidentiality regarding the personal data gathered in accordance with the applicable legislation.

## Duration and modifications

VOXBONE reserves the right to revise its privacy policy at any time and in response to changes introduced by applicable data protection laws. We will notify our Customers whenever we modify this policy.  

Last updated: **  February 2018**
